<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>The Craft Of Open Source</title><description><![CDATA[<p>Welcome to&nbsp;<em>The Craft of Open Source</em>, hosted by Ben Rometsch, Co-Founder and CEO of Flagsmith. This bi-weekly show is focused on the ins and outs of the Open Source Software Community. Join Ben as he speaks with the brightest minds that have brought us some of the most adopted technologies on earth. Each episode is an interview with creators, maintainers, entrepreneurs, and key contributors to the open source community.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>We will cover critical topics for open source developers, contributors and entrepreneurs such as: Which open source licenses are best if you want to start a business at some point? How did people start their projects? What was the first commit? Did people start their projects for business or a different reason? How can you build an organic community around new projects? How can you create a business and still be open source? Where is open source headed?</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The technologies that we plan to profile will range from huge projects like React.js, Ansible, Git, PHP, Kafka, GitHub, Java, Python, Javascript, Redis, Kubernetes, VisualStudio, TensorFlow, Android, Apache, Spinnaker, Azure, and many more.</p><p>&nbsp;</p><p>The types of licenses that we plan to profile will include: GNU General Public License (GPL), The Apache License, Microsoft Public License (Ms-Pl), Berkeley Software Distribution (BSD), Common Development and Distribution License (CDDL), Eclipse Public License (EPL), and MIT License.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/ctUnKYYRE.png"></itunes:image><language>en-us</language><itunes:category text="Technology"></itunes:category><itunes:category text="Business"><itunes:category text="Entrepreneurship"></itunes:category></itunes:category><itunes:category text="News"><itunes:category text="Tech News"></itunes:category></itunes:category><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><itunes:author>Ben Rometsch, CEO, Flagsmith</itunes:author><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/</link><itunes:owner><itunes:name>Anna Redbond</itunes:name><itunes:email>anna.redbond@flagsmith.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:type>episodic</itunes:type><copyright>Copyright 2023 Ben Rometsch | The Craft Of Open Source | All Rights Reserved</copyright><item><title>Malcolm Matalka: Co-Founder at Terrateam</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/s8OEzeGS6/media/aoy6NbMq2.mp3" length="48605546" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>s8OEzeGS6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3038</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/terrateam</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">Interview With Malcolm Matalka: Co-Founder, Terrateam</span></p><p><br></p><p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">Ben Rometsch chats with </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/malcolm-matalka-a6527382/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Malcolm Matalka</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">, co-founder of </span><a href="https://terrateam.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Terrateam</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">, to discuss the company’s inception and its eventual shift to open source. Together, they discuss how his frustrations with the click ops approach prompted Malcolm to create his own team to disrupt the system and pave the way for much more innovative methods. He opens up about the challenges they faced due to the licensing changes of HashiCrop and how it led to the creation of OpenTofu. The two also emphasize the undeniable dynamic of community-driven projects and how they offer people options and opportunities to adjust, transform, and collaborate.</span></p><p><br></p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/sNmDbCyg_.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>74</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Sam Stepanyan, OWASP London Chapter Leader &amp; OWASP Global Board Member</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/DeBgn1Cx2/media/u1ba4A123.mp3" length="51216102" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>DeBgn1Cx2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3201</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/owasp</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">With almost every transaction being done through the internet, your personal information and finances must be protected at all costs from hackers and scammers. Therefore, cybersecurity is important now more than ever. Leading the charge in keeping the digital world safe and secure is </span><a href="https://owasp.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">OWASP</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">, a non-profit organization working mainly on software security. Joining this episode is Sam Stepanyan from the OWASP London Chapter who emphasizes why cybersecurity must be accomplished at the start of development, not as an afterthought. He also explains why education on cybersecurity is severely lacking and what should be done to make it a staple subject in schools.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/B292lUVOF.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>73</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Chris Villa, Co-Founder of Puck &amp; Measured</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/iOw1Zy1zo/media/UkYCVi0wb.mp3" length="48012878" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>iOw1Zy1zo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jan 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3001</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/puck-measured</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">Interview With Chris Villa: Co-Founder, Puck &amp; Measured</span></p><p>Puck, an open-source project, has exploded in popularity, becoming a major focus for Chris Villa and his team. But how do you balance a runaway open-source hit with the demands of running a consultancy? Join Ben Rometsch as he sits down with Chris Villa, co-founder of both <a href="https://puckeditor.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Puck</a><u style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);"> </u>and <a href="https://measured.co/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Measured</a>, to dissect this very dilemma. Chris reveals the fascinating origin story of Puck, its meteoric rise, and the overwhelming "pull" from the community that signals a powerful product-market fit. Find out Chris and his team's bold plan to spin Puck out as its entity, poised to take the project to even greater heights.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/4h07aZjLB.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>72</itunes:episode></item><item><title>James McLeod: Open Source Program Lead at NatWest Group</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/BpN7qppSo/media/EFGnvmR-L.mp3" length="54385487" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>BpN7qppSo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3399</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/natwest</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Joining this episode is James McLeod, Open Source Program Lead at NatWest Group. He looks back on his career journey, from his role at the Linux Foundation, his efforts in scaling the FINOS project, to the creation of London.js. Reflecting on the many lessons throughout his professional life, James stressed the importance of proper data documentation and education to make open source more accessible to the public. He also explained what it takes for engineers to fully embrace their roles in the wider digital ecosystem, making open source an essential platform for career advancement and development.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/-FBgpA_u8.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>72</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Moritz Klack &amp; Christopher Möller: Co-Founders, xyflow</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/E16kGjBLK/media/v5fZRz9nl.mp3" length="33297830" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>E16kGjBLK</guid><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2081</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/xyflow</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">This episode features Moritz Klack and Christopher Möller, Co-Founders of </span><a href="https://xyflow.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">xyflow</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;">. They look back on their career journey leading to their current company, from developing </span><a href="https://webkid.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">webkid</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;">, creating </span><a href="https://datablocks.pro/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Datablocks</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;">, and launching React Flow. They discuss their transition from agency work to open source, their pricing strategies, and the importance of community feedback. Moritz and Christopher also bare their plans for the future and what trends in the digital space they are most excited about.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/V76zmbgda.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>71</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Konstantin Vinogradov, General Partner At Runa Capital</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/7bflFiR1P/media/HZxdHop2y.mp3" length="41822064" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>7bflFiR1P</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2614</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/runa-capital</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">With their keen eye for innovation and their knack for spotting the next big thing, </span><a href="https://runacap.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Runa Capital</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;"> is at the forefront of the tech revolution. In this episode, Ben Rometsch delves into the world of open-source software with </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kvinogradov/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Konstantin Vinogradov</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;">, General Partner at Runa Capital. Konstantin reflects on the founding principles of Runa Capital and its commitment to investing in open source and AI technologies. He also discusses the potential for open-source endowments to provide long-term support for open-source projects, drawing parallels to the funding mechanisms of universities. Join them as they delve into the intersection of technology, investment, and the future of open source in the digital age.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/Lte3zeAYZ.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>69</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Ivan Burazin: Co-Founder of Daytona</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/GGL5RxE-S/media/asDcxK-CX.mp3" length="47630848" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>GGL5RxE-S</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2977</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/daytona</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ivanburazin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Ivan Burazin</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);"> proudly presents </span><a href="https://www.daytona.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Daytona</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">, a secure open-source development environment manager that allows developers to tailor their environments according to their specific needs. Ivan looks back on how their company started as an enterprise product before becoming an open-source project for individual developers. He breaks down its most important features, particularly those that assure ease of use, clarity, and simplicity. Ivan also explains how automation and AI tools could further improve Daytona, all while balancing user privacy and accurate data collection.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/QAKs_H2vP.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>68</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Chuck Carpenter: Founder, Shepherd Pro &amp; Host, Whiskey Web and Whatnot</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/s3D4DXUUp/media/Bx39pQUZT.mp3" length="41235237" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>s3D4DXUUp</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2577</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/shepherd-pro</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Buckle up for a journey into Shepherd! In this episode, Chuck Carpenter, the founder of <a href="https://shepherdpro.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Shepherd Pro</a> and host of Whiskey Web and Whatnot, joins Ben Rometsch to delve into Shepherd and Shepherd JS, an influential open-source library for creating interactive guides in JavaScript. Chuck shares his deep involvement over seven years as a maintainer, highlighting Shepherd’s evolution from its origins at HubSpot to becoming a robust tool with broad community adoption. Don’t miss Chuck’s insights on Shepherd’s edge in the user experience space, its business potential, and his vision for leading the developer community forward.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/afVoRzWnN.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>66</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Julius Volz, CoFounder of Prometheus</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/pVUFqPmd3/media/DzUdx1CAC.mp3" length="51571378" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>pVUFqPmd3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3223</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/prometheus</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Managing a modern application landscape can be a balancing act. Enter <a href="https://prometheus.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Prometheus</a>, an open-source champion for monitoring and alerting. In this episode, <a href="https://de.linkedin.com/in/julius-volz" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">Julius Volz</a>, co-founder of Prometheus and founder of <a href="https://promlabs.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);">PromLabs</a>, joins Ben Rometsch to discuss the origins and evolution of Prometheus. Julius traces its inception to his early days at Google and SoundCloud, where the need for a robust monitoring system inspired Prometheus. He explains how Prometheus revolutionized monitoring with its pull-based approach, powerful PromQL query language, and flexible data model, enabling effective monitoring, alerting, and automation. Discover how Prometheus continues to shape the future of monitoring!&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/fLi2ir8Ky.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>66</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Jonathan Schneider: Co-Founder, Moderne</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/zOszehZZw/media/6hFQLXo_y.mp3" length="41368992" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>zOszehZZw</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2586</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/moderne</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Moderne is a pioneer in the field of mass-scale automated code refactoring, and it has some pretty interesting origins. In this episode, co-founder Jonathan Schneider talks about the genesis of Moderne, how he started his open-source journey from being an engineer at Netflix, and their current initiatives, including some interesting developments at Openhaus. Tune in for more details!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/eiLFfOGMR.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>65</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Deb Goodkin, Executive Director at The FreeBSD Foundation</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/D-JRgVlkN/media/LUoY1W-XS.mp3" length="45040337" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>D-JRgVlkN</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2815</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/freebsd-foundation</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">Ever wondered how the backbone of streaming giants like Netflix or gaming consoles like Sony PlayStation ticks? Dive deep with us in this episode as we unravel the legacy and impact of FreeBSD, one of the unsung heroes of the tech world. Join us in an insightful conversation with </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/deb-goodkin-b282924a/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Deb Goodkin</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">, the Executive Director of the </span><a href="https://freebsdfoundation.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">FreeBSD Foundation</a><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">, as we explore the history, evolution, and significance of FreeBSD. From its roots in Berkeley UNIX to its integral role in modern technology, Deb sheds light on why this powerful, cohesive operating system stands out from Linux and how its permissive licensing has attracted major players. Discover the fascinating story behind FreeBSD's stability, performance, and community-driven development. Tune in for more intriguing details and expert insights you won't want to miss!</span></p><p><br></p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/wuLB0fqVx.jpg"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>64</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Eddie Jaoude, Open Source Consultant</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/yrB7UwBCh/media/K_FvmrUP9.mp3" length="49077000" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>yrB7UwBCh</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3067</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/eddie-jaoude</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">Success is not just about focusing on the grind. It is also about applying yourself every single day and letting your efforts compound over time. In this episode, open source consultant&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/eddiejaoude" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Eddie Jaoude</a>&nbsp;shares how he applied this mindset in his own career path. Joining Ben Rometsch, he explains how he successfully built a strong online following through his edutainment content about the open source industry, especially on Twitter. Eddie also opens up on how he takes care of his mental health as he deals with online trolls, toxic feedback, and negative comments on social media every single day.</p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/jJdS4w2fG.jpg"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>63</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Ari Zilka, CEO of MyDecisive.ai</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/jRwpsB72V/media/RXX6t5sCU.mp3" length="42655874" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>jRwpsB72V</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2666</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/mydecisive-ai</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>In this episode of The Craft of Open Source, Ari Zilka describes his transition from his previous projects to founding a new company that aims to improve control over observability data in IT. He identifies issues with current observability tools, such as high costs and lack of flexibility, and propose using OpenTelemetry to offer a more customizable and manageable system. This new approach gives DevOps teams better tools for handling large amounts of data, ensuring security, and optimizing costs without relying on proprietary solutions. Tune in to learn more about MyDecisive.ai and Ari's outlook on the open-source space!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/5hVgC6YdY.png"></itunes:image></item><item><title>Birk Jernström, CEO/Founder at Polar</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/pQgt7ZQLw/media/oTXq-cI4a.mp3" length="38444111" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>pQgt7ZQLw</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2403</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/polar</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">Ben Rometsch sits down with <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/birknilson/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Birk Jernström</a>, who shares the genesis story of <a href="https://polar.sh/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Polar</a>, a creator platform for developers. He explains how he established his company using his experiences and expertise gained from Tictail and Shopify. Birk discusses how he changes the status quo for open-source developers in terms of working on their passions full-time and independently. He also talks about the power of changing your perspectives and how he handles the needs of every single person down the dependency tree.</p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/MLZuVQs48.jpg"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>62</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Heather Meeker, Founding Partner at OSS Capital</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/pFpa4_z1o/media/fa3wXfRtr.mp3" length="52722427" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>pFpa4_z1o</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Apr 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3295</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/oss-capital-pt-2</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>These past few years, open-source has been on the fast track to dominating the software market. It might sound contradictory to many people, but open-source is big business. A project’s source code may be free, but the products generated from that source code can certainly be commercialized. If you’re a project developer, therein lies the potential for economic benefit, if only you had the financial backing and business know-how. Heather Meeker, Founding Partner at OSS Capital returns to the show to talk about the different aspects of open-source business, from finding venture capital backing to navigating the intricacies of branding and product positioning. Tune in to this informative episode!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/6udKe7nXD.mp3"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>61</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Joe Duffy, CEO and Founder of Pulumi</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/rlXyIu6Mt/media/KHIJVVdVe.mp3" length="35485791" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>rlXyIu6Mt</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2218</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/pulumi</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: black;">Join us in this episode, where we take a deep dive into the story of </span><a href="https://www.pulumi.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Pulumi</a><span style="color: black;"> with its CEO and Founder, </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/joejduffy/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Joe Duffy</a><span style="color: black;">. From its inception in 2016 with the ambitious goal of simplifying cloud infrastructure management through the creation of a new programming language, Joe takes us on a journey into the team’s evolution that helped Pulumi become what it is today. He talks about the intricacies of Pulumi Cloud, insights product, and the strategic alignment of Pulumi’s business model with the community's success. Get ready for a candid conversation as Joe shares his insights on overcoming challenges, chasing future goals, and dreaming big about an open ecosystem in cloud infrastructure management. Tune in now and discover how Pulumi is shaping the future of cloud development!</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/xI0N53EaH.mp3"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>60</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Oleg Nenashev, Governance Board/Core Maintainer, Jenkins</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/09eYmvPda/media/ZQTbuwCfN.mp3" length="35103372" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>09eYmvPda</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Jan 2024 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2194</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/jenkins-wiremock</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Jenkins, an open-source stalwart and a foundational project of the Continuous Delivery Foundation, underwent a transformative journey towards independence within the foundation. In this conversation with Oleg Nenashev, Governance Board/Core Maintainer, we navigate through the significance of feature flags in continuous integration and delivery, culminating in excitement about the potential standardization through the open feature project. Shifting gears, the conversation delves into WireMock, a widely-used API mocking tool, exploring its capabilities, commercial extensions, and upcoming improvements in version 3. Oleg emphasizes collaboration and alignment across diverse languages and repositories. The conversation concludes by spotlighting Penpot, an open-source design platform, as a noteworthy project. Join in for a comprehensive exploration of Jenkins, feature flags, WireMock, and the broader open-source landscape.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/Pc-DB8fk-.mp3"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>59</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Shauli Rozen, CEO &amp; Cofounder of ARMO</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/ml3alMUGW/media/8f6Erz4E9.mp3" length="32111607" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>ml3alMUGW</guid><pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2007</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/armo</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>With the digital world evolving nonstop, keeping your data secure must be one of your top priorities at all times. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/shaulirozen/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Shauli Rozen</a> of <a href="https://www.armosec.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">ARMO</a> explains how they help end-users and developers address their Kubernetes security needs through <a href="https://github.com/kubescape/kubescape/releases" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Kubescape</a>. In this episode, he explains how their software applies security remediation without breaking the application, bringing DevOps and security together. Shauli also shares the various projects they studied and gathered ideas from in developing Kubescape and how it helps solve the ever-transforming security issues of the open-source industry.</p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/iV1vtk049.mp3"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>58</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Didier Lopes, CEO and Founder of OpenBB</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/NxEW2ZGuz/media/EI5NbxHDg.mp3" length="43336347" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>NxEW2ZGuz</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2708</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/openbb</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>OpenBB stands at the crossroads of innovation, uniting open-source spirit with financial prowess to empower every individual. In this episode of our podcast, Didier Lopes discusses OpenBB, a revolutionary platform aiming to democratize access to financial data. From its inception to its evolution into a versatile financial data hub, Didier shows how OpenBB thrives as a bridge connecting financial data for everyone. Join us as we explore the potential future directions for OpenBB, envisioning an ecosystem where financial data is seamlessly accessible, customized, and affordable for all types of users. Tune in now!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/AG8kyJ_hB.mp3"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>57</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Emily Omier, Positioning Strategy Consultant for Open Source Startups</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/m5pDNdNFp/media/rxrT_roNi.mp3" length="45229869" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>m5pDNdNFp</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Nov 2023 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2826</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/emily-omier</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">Positioning for open source startups is directly connected not just to their free resource but also their commercial strategy. How should business leaders approach this to yield the best results and maintain a well-performing team? In this episode, Positioning Strategy Consultant for open source startups <a href="https://www.emilyomier.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Emily Omier</a> talks about keeping teams in alignment and in the same feedback loop. She explains how this approach can help them navigate through the complex mind games involved in these projects and why she considers the government as the best open source clients out there. Emily also shares how she sees the industry progress in the next half decade in terms of dominance and refutes three fallacies about open source projects.</p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/7PHRex2no.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>56</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Pete Hunt, CEO of Elementl/Dagster</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/DoLhOQW2n/media/yHlu3p3Mr.mp3" length="42436871" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>DoLhOQW2n</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2652</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/elementl-dagster</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Data is the name of the game in today’s world. But with the amount of data sources today, how do you sift through and get the data you want? A data pipeline is the answer, and within that pipeline is a data orchestrator. Today’s guest, Pete Hunt, is the CEO of Elementl, the company behind the open-source orchestration platform, Dagster. He joins Ben Rometsch to tell us all about Elementl and Dagster as well as his career journey that took him across Facebook, Instagram, Smyte, and Twitter. In this current fluctuating environment, we can say it is a feat for a company to be able to raise money. Just this year, Elementl was able to raise $33 million Series B for Dagster. Find out how they are able to achieve this, what they are doing for data orchestration, and where they are heading in the future. Tune in to this episode to not miss out!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/k1PbN9eNg.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>55</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Hannah Aubry, Community Manager at Fastly/Fast Forward</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/BvPs4vW04/media/AiZUQMyuOX.mp3" length="24972668" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>BvPs4vW04</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Oct 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>1561</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/fastly</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Celebrating the unsung heroes of open source, Fastly is shaping a future where technology meets kindness, collaboration, and a better internet for all. In this episode, we interview Hannah Aubry who shares how they are doing these things by undergoing significant innovation and a rebrand to become <a href="https://www.fastly.com/fast-forward" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Fast Forward</a>. She sheds light on the incredible contributions of the most skilled individuals behind open-source technology and how organizations like theirs are stepping up to empower them. Hannah also covers how Fastly is championing change in this particular space while celebrating the most talented builders of the digital world.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/9aKIJU3Bv.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>54</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Misko Hevery, CTO at Builder.io</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/UvQE-mn9L/media/u7XD84nc65.mp3" length="41731577" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>UvQE-mn9L</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2608</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/builder-io</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>In web development, we're not just crafting code; we're shaping the digital world's future. In this episode, we interview&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/misko-hevery-3883b1/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Misko Hevery</a>, co-founder of&nbsp;<a href="https://www.builder.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Builder.io</a>, about the landscape of web development and the cutting-edge Qwik framework. Misko starts by diving into Builder.io. Discover how it aims to bridge the gap between visual web content creation and developers' expertise, creating a win-win situation for both parties. Moving on to the world of Qwik, Misko expounds on its unique approach of delivering components rather than JSON data, resulting in unparalleled user experiences. Explore how Qwik challenges the conventions of existing frameworks and offers a fresh perspective on web development. Throughout the episode, Misko also explores many topics, such as the sustainability of open-source materials, what’s next for Builder.io, and more. Tune in to this conversation now and embark on a journey that could reshape the way you think about building for the web. Don't miss it!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/Tf8unkhnx.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>53</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Peer Richelsen, Co-Founder of Cal.com</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/vey1wFF_7/media/LHfgiGy6z.mp3" length="41714846" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>vey1wFF_7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2607</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/cal-com</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>It takes great effort to build something with the fastest star growth count. And with Cal.com, they have the greatest domain, mission, and product that made that growth possible! In this episode<span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">,&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/peer-richelsen-221233138/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Peer Richelsen</a>, the Co-Founder of&nbsp;<a href="http://cal.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Cal.com</a>, takes us into the scheduling infrastructure they’ve built to help everyone focus on their meeting, not making meetings. Peer also touches on what he needs to qualify as an Open Scheduling. Meet Cal.com today and make booking easier for you.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/Uyz27b3Db.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>52</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Darko Fabijan, Co-Founder at Semaphore</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/YT63MpXxK/media/zahFyZR1uZ.mp3" length="33485123" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>YT63MpXxK</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2092</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/semaphore</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="background-color: transparent; color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">Do you spend so much time building and running your pipeline? That doesn’t have to be the case anymore. In this episode,&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/darkofabijan/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Darko Fabijan</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;">, the co-founder of&nbsp;</span><a href="https://semaphoreci.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Semaphore</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26); background-color: transparent;">, shares the efforts Darko and his team went into improving Semaphore products to serve their clients. Through the development of their products, it minimizes the time spent in running your pipeline with CI/CD Solutions. Darko also explains how Semaphore On-Premise functions as your team grows. Join us in this episode and learn how Semaphore makes development teams move faster.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/sFXkPLCIY.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>51</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Alois Reitbauer, Chief Technology Strategist at Dynatrace</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/5P-21vLdN/media/xdhiWBbPE.mp3" length="36331427" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>5P-21vLdN</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2270</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/dynatrace</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to technology, having reliable monitoring is crucial to ensuring a positive user experience and the seamless operation of an app. <a href="https://www.dynatrace.com/%20" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Dynatrace</a> is a company that specializes in enhancing the digital environment of organizations with their cutting-edge solutions, unlocking the full potential of digital intelligence. Their innovative platform has the power to propel your business to new heights. In this episode, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/aloisreitbauer/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Alois Reitbauer</a>, the Chief Technology Strategist at Dynatrace, dives into how they discern the fundamental specifications and overall project vision beyond its individual components. He also explains the development of Open Feature and how collaborative efforts within the team contribute to project success. Alois reveals the instrumental role of the open-source canvas within the company. Let's embark on a journey exploring the endless possibilities in this thrilling era of digital intelligence, powered by Dynatrace.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/xdc4VEWDX.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>50</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Justin Abrahms, Principal Architect/Governing Board of OpenFeature</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/IfQXZpyWA/media/Na7FT1GoLn.mp3" length="33628187" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>IfQXZpyWA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2102</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/openfeature-pt-2</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>From passion projects to corporate powerhouses, open source has evolved into a force that shapes the tech industry's future, driven by the collective efforts of passionate individuals and visionary companies. In this episode, we interview Justin Abrahms, the Principal Architect/Governing Board of OpenFeature, to discuss the diverse landscape of open-source development and its impact on the tech industry. He discusses the early days of open source, when companies like Google and eBay were just beginning to recognize their potential. Justin explained how these companies, although lacking the breakout successes of Kubernetes, played a crucial role in the open-source ecosystem. Yet he believes there's room for improvement in open-source management, advocating for a more systematic approach to stewardship and organizational support. Diving deeper, Justin explores the driving forces behind different approaches to open-source projects. Steering toward the future, Justin explores the potential paradigm shifts in open source, including how Rust rises to prominence and more. Join us in understanding the evolution of open source, from its humble beginnings to the present day.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/rJM0l6dQP.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>49</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Max Howell, CEO of tea.xyz</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/ARisfOJoJ/media/OkqLrO6in.mp3" length="41946399" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>ARisfOJoJ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2621</itunes:duration><link>http://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/tea-xyz</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Tea is the catalyst that shifts open source from a labor of love to a sustainable revolution, ensuring that the creators behind our digital infrastructure receive the funding they deserve. In this episode, we sit down with Max Howell, the visionary mind behind the <a href="http://tea.xyz/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);"><u>Tea</u></a>&nbsp;Package Manager, and explore his journey from building the widely popular Homebrew (Brew) to embarking on a mission to fix open-source remuneration. With passion and determination, Max shares his vision for Tea, a groundbreaking solution aimed at reshaping the funding landscape for open-source projects. He walks through the intricate workings of Tea, where voluntary donations are replaced by a unique investment model that rewards stakeholders with a stake in the system. By leveraging blockchain technology, Tea creates a direct link between funding and open source, ensuring that those who contribute receive their fair share. Don't miss out on exploring the power of blockchain technology and its capacity to transform the world of open-source software. Tune in now!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/iZrInRoxW.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>49</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Rob Moffat, Senior Technical Architect at FINOS</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/NGmkRdXAs/media/AbY75bmKfB.mp3" length="37073003" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>NGmkRdXAs</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2317</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/finos</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>For the longest time, financial services organizations have largely been consumers of open-source technology, and they haven’t been very keen in moving towards the contribution side. But things are starting to change as a lot of organizations in the space are beginning to give more weight to the idea of using their resources to help maintain and improve the open-source projects that they use. FINOS leads the way in promoting open innovation in the financial services industry. Joining us on the podcast today to tell us more about it is the nonprofit’s Senior Technical Architect, Rob Moffat. In this conversation, Rob tells us how FINOS provides open-source software solutions that help address common industry challenges and drive innovation that benefits all organizations involved. Join in and learn the prospects lying in wait for the future of open-source fintech!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/JWpuGT2Bh.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>47</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Kamran Ahmed, Founder of roadmap.sh</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/38eu8ldw0/media/_9x-f7llO.mp3" length="37191346" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>38eu8ldw0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2324</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/roadmap-sh</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Many of us struggle with where to start whenever we embark on a new journey. For developers contending in such a fast-paced and ever-growing environment, it can be confusing to figure out what to learn next. This episode’s guest is breaking down this barrier. Kamran Ahmed created <a href="https://roadmap.sh/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">roadmap.sh</a> to help developers find their path and help them learn and grow in their careers. Kamran joins us to share his remarkable journey as the founder of this great resource project. Initially met with mixed responses, his brainchild has blossomed into a thriving community-driven initiative. Kamran shares insights into maintaining this community approach, partnering with organizations, and hosting the project on GitHub. With an impressive user base of 700,000 monthly visitors and a newsletter with 250,000 subscribers, Kamran discusses the challenges and strategies behind managing such remarkable growth. We also gain valuable insights into their creative process as well as their plans for income generation. Tune in to discover the inspiring story of roadmap.sh and its incredible success.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/TddHrZtUA.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>46</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Emre Baran, CEO &amp; Co-Founder At Cerbos</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/z7wM7Qkxln/media/4Gce1d42c.mp3" length="43962358" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>z7wM7Qkxln</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2747</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/cerbos</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: black;">Authorization can be a time-consuming process, but you can never get away from it because it is just as essential to your product and business. What if there is a way to make this easy? With </span><a href="https://cerbos.dev/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Cerbos</a><span style="color: black;">, that is possible. Cerbos is the authorization layer for software applications to be able to quickly and securely implement roles and permissions. In this episode, its CEO and Founder </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/emrebaran/?originalSubdomain=uk" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Emre Baran</a><span style="color: black;"> joins us to help us get to know the work they are doing and how they have built and grown it. He talks about decoupling authorization, making life easy for developers to implement this. He also breaks down the differences between authorization, authentication, and feature flagging as well as the benefits of open source to developing trust. Emre fills us with so many insights about the world of Cerbos and how they are making authorization simpler. So tune in to this conversation to learn more!</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/ZOltThPGD.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>45</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Daniel Lenton, CEO Of Ivy</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/Gx_2Mh90k/media/i4as37FYl.mp3" length="46165707" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>Gx_2Mh90k</guid><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2885</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/ivy/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: black;">There is fragmentation in the field of AI that no one seems to be taking too seriously. </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/daniellenton/?originalSubdomain=uk" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Daniel Lenton</a><span style="color: black;">, the CEO of </span><a href="https://unify.ai/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Ivy</a><span style="color: black;">, observed this, finding so many frameworks, models, infrastructures, and hardware that make it hard for collaboration. Helping solve this problem, Ivy was created to unify all Machine Learning (ML) frameworks. In this episode, he tells us how they made it possible to fit these pieces together. Daniel also takes us through his journey prior to Ivy, the walls they hit in the labs, and the lessons they learned overcoming them. Talking about Ivy’s growth, he then shares their success in GitHub and Discord and where they see they’re heading in the future. For more insights about AI, ML frameworks, and open-source technology, join Daniel in this conversation. Find out how Ivy uniquely allows you to bring any model, library, or function into one line of code for your project.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/XFAXA1CNs.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>44</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Special Episode - Ben Rometsch, Founder &amp; CEO Of Flagsmith And The Craft Of Open Source </title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/uO8u9ZDay/media/cpRX407Z0.mp3" length="45849312" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>uO8u9ZDay</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2866</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/ben-rometsch-flagsmith/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://flagsmith.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Flagsmith's</a> CEO, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/benrometsch/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Ben Rometsch</a>, is a true champion of open source. His software revolution is turning heads among developers, by unlocking the true potential of simplicity and sustainability in the digital world. In this special interview episode, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jasonbosco/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Jason Bosco</a> from Type Sense takes charge and conducts an exciting conversation with Ben Rometsch. Today’s episode unravels the story behind Flagsmith and the pivotal moments that drove its creation. Jason probes Ben with insightful questions, exploring his decision to embrace open source from the start and the strategic considerations around its future monetization. Together, they discuss the significance of self-hosting for customers and the synergies it brings to software deployment. Ben shares how he approaches positioning the product, bridging the gap between proprietary solutions and an open-source alternative. They also delve into the realm of developer marketing, exploring effective channels and lessons learned. Don't miss out on the exciting glimpse into Flag Smith's future roadmap and the enduring philosophy of simplicity and sustainability in software development. Tune in now!</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/3ZAocFqF7.png"></itunes:image><itunes:episode>43</itunes:episode></item><item><title>NanoVMs</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/fSdMLvaX-/media/hZLWR826aZ.mp3" length="42970832" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>fSdMLvaX-</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2686</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/nanovms/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>This whole idea of having an operating system that runs many different programs on one computer is completely outdated and doesn't reflect reality whatsoever. The question is, “What would an operating system look like for something in 2020 to serve up the software?” That's where <a href="https://nanovms.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">NanoVMs</a> come in with a unikernel concept. Today, its CEO, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ianeyberg/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Ian Eyberg</a>, takes us into a deep dive into unikernels and how they function. Tune in to discover how to efficiently manage virtual machines and create a truly agile environment for your software development.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>42</itunes:episode></item><item><title>CapRover</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/52Y62P7Ah/media/epEwGwh2C.mp3" length="36879313" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>52Y62P7Ah</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2304</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/caprover/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">In this episode, we welcome <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kasra-bigdeli-68b6803b" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Kasra Bigdeli</a>, Engineering Manager at <a href="https://caprover.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">CapRover</a>. He shares how he built an open-source version of Heroku that features one-click apps. He explains how he designed it to be newbie-friendly: easy to navigate and full of contextual help. Kasra also talks about using only organic techniques in marketing CapRover, and now its community is naturally growing with more than a hundred projects.</p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>41</itunes:episode></item><item><title>React-Admin</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/QKNp3m4R4/media/J2FkEUg5L.mp3" length="39047076" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>QKNp3m4R4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2440</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/react-admin</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>When you create something you love, it feels good to give it away for people to tinker around and do great things with it. That is what is open-source is all about. But what happens when the cost of maintaining an open-source project becomes too high to sustain? Some people would abandon it, but not <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/FZaninotto/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Francois Zaninotto</a>, CEO of <a href="https://marmelab.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Marmelab</a>. Realizing the untapped potential of <a href="https://marmelab.com/react-admin/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">React-Admin</a>, he managed to build a sustainable business model from an open-source core. Find out how he did it in this conversation. Plus, get a glimpse of his other project, <a href="http://www.greenframe.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">GreenFrame.io</a>, <span style="color: black; --darkreader-inline-color: #ebe0cd;" data-darkreader-inline-color="">which allows users to estimate the carbon emissions linked to user scenarios on a web application</span> and use that information to create a carbon reduction strategy.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>40</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Project Calico</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/Y2TPALaff/media/K3ZMDjzkmJ.mp3" length="36062379" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>Y2TPALaff</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2023 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2253</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/project-calico</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">Ben Rometsch and Matt Althauser sit down with Shaun Campton, Principal Engineer at <a href="https://www.tigera.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Tigera</a>, who shares his experiences as a core developer on <a href="https://www.tigera.io/project-calico/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Project Calico</a>. He talks about their origins of moving out of the era of doing forklift moves into OpenStack and down the development of network splitting, focusing more on a dynamic firewall approach. He opens up on his experiences writing their first 10,000 lines of code, their identity-based policy, and the value they are offering to clients. Shaun also provides insights on what may be next for Kubernetes and how open-source projects must get ready for any change ahead.</p><p><br></p>]]></description></item><item><title>OpenFeature</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/rKpE5AxlC/media/fm_6ldPdA.mp3" length="43920286" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>rKpE5AxlC</guid><pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 13:06:17 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2745</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/openfeature-with-mike-beamer-and-todd-baert</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>As simple as they seem, feature flags cannot be underestimated. The more you dive into what it offers, the more you realize how much it can clean up your code base. Mike Beamer and&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/todd-baert-739b1bb8/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Todd Baert</a>&nbsp;saw the value it could further provide and founded&nbsp;<a href="https://openfeature.dev/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">OpenFeature</a>. OpenFeature is an open standard for feature flag management, created to support a robust feature flag ecosystem using cloud-native technologies. In this episode, they share with us the work they are doing as well as the genesis of OpenFeature as part of Dynatrace. Mike and Todd then talk about their vision, measuring their progress and success, and what they find exciting about open source projects. What is more, they discuss the diversity of the community in the open source space, highlighting the tremendous value in bringing passions, talents, and support together.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/-mZ-7w2zx.png"></itunes:image></item><item><title>Vercel</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/hgUb1K3v9/media/Go-li4kNx.mp3" length="44902183" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>hgUb1K3v9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2022 12:43:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2806</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/vercel-with-guillermo-rauch</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: black;">When </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/guillermo-rauch-b834b917b/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Guillermo Rauch</a><span style="color: black;"> started </span><a href="https://vercel.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Vercel</a><span style="color: black;">, people asked him, “what came first, the idea of simplifying global delivery or the idea of creating a framework?” He answered, “what about both?” Guillermo explored the conception of a system where it gets better. The more it gets global, the more resilient and dynamic it becomes that the operations go away. In this episode, he tells us how he took on these two problems, watched them co-evolve, and founded Vercel—a platform for frontend developers, providing the speed and reliability innovators need to create at the moment of inspiration. Guillermo shares how they are democratizing access to the server side rendering and lowering the cost with edge functions. He also taps into the importance of developer experience, the challenges they faced along the way, and the future Vercel is heading.</span></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Bagisto</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/2VrcLsl0w/media/nTz7JZoeTj.mp3" length="40577129" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>2VrcLsl0w</guid><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 07:20:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2536</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/bagisto</link><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Laravelis one of the most popular PHP web frameworks today and has gained much traction worldwide. However, one thing it doesn't have is a proper e-commerce system. Saurav Pathak took this gap between Laravel and the developer community as a business opportunity. He joins Ben Rometsch to share how he bootstrapped a company called Magisto, an open-source eCommerce ecosystem that provides reliable support to the merchant community. Saurav explains the community management strategies that spelled success for their team, their marketing tactics, and how they drew inspiration(and perform alongside) eCommerce giants like Shopify.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Datastax</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/C-G67ldBe/media/KEOP3e0tX.mp3" length="48709809" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>C-G67ldBe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 10:10:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3044</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/datastax</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">Apache Cassandra paved the way for today's biggest digital platforms to scale into the much bigger global scene. Patrick McFadin of <a href="https://www.datastax.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Datastax</a> is one of the people involved in this open-source project and saw first-hand how it burst into the world. He joins Ben Rometsch to share how Cassandra was developed, the many challenges they faced in its optimization, its relationship with Datastax, and how it changed database engine creation and data modeling. Patrick also talks about the measures they are implementing to continuously improve Cassandra and limit open-source access to ensure quality.</p><p><br></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Mike McNeil, CEO @ Fleet</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/lb9_naTM9/media/mSywJmy1e.mp3" length="30535659" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>lb9_naTM9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>1908</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/mike-mcneil-ceo-fleet</link><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://fleetdm.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Fleet</u></a>&nbsp;is the most widely used open-source OSQuery manager. It allows you to get accurate data from every endpoint in your organization and allow organizations to have complete control over their data. Fleet has been instrumental in businesses, for it is a scalable and resilient platform that manages your workloads. In this episode, <a href="https://github.com/mikermcneil%20" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Mike McNeil</u></a>, the CEO of Fleet, explains how Fleet and <a href="https://osquery.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>OSQuery</u></a>&nbsp;can significantly help your organization. Listen to this episode and learn more from Mike as he shares more information about Fleet as an open-source OSQuery manager.</p>]]></description><itunes:image href="https://feeds.podetize.com/RgkFGtidw.jpg"></itunes:image></item><item><title>rocket.chat W/ Co-Founder And CEO Gabriel Engel</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/fObnFC5as/media/8V_ChNAcP.mp3" length="60349135" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>fObnFC5as</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3772</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/rocketchat-with-co-founder-and-ceo-gabriel-engel</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Join Ben Rometsch as he talks to <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/gabrielengel/?originalSubdomain=br" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Gabriel Engel</a>, the founder and CEO of Rocket Chat. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>Temporal w/ Co-Founder and CEO Maxim Fateev &amp; Head of Product Ryland Goldstein</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/V64PdzW3H/media/etC1-ahNj.mp3" length="48162786" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>V64PdzW3H</guid><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 09:11:31 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3010</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/temporal-w-co-founder-and-ceo-maxim-fateev-and-head-of-product-ryland-goldstein</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://temporal.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Temporal's</a>&nbsp;Co-Founder and CEO,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/fateev/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Maxim Fateev</a>, and Head of Product,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ryland-goldstein-3467b710a/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Ryland Goldstein</a> sit down with Ben to talk about open source and the origin of their project. Temporal is a microservice orchestration platform which enables developers to build scalable applications without sacrificing productivity or reliability. Temporal server executes units of application logic, Workflows, in a resilient manner that automatically handles intermittent failures, and retries failed operations. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>Greg Hayes, Creator Of Dask</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/d4GaNjt0P/media/qSI4o7GqN.mp3" length="28320186" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>d4GaNjt0P</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Jun 2022 10:35:07 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>1770</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/greg-hayes-dask</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Greg Hayes, Director of Engineering at Coiled joins Ben to talk about the Dask project. Dask makes it easy to scale the Python libraries that you know and love like NumPy, pandas and scikit-learn. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>RackN W/ Founder And CEO Rob Hirschfeld</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/7Z3srdKtQ/media/AxQ6dqLUY.mp3" length="43753231" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>7Z3srdKtQ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 07 Jun 2022 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2735</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/rackn-w-founder-and-ceo-rob-hirschfeld/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/rhirschfeld/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Rob Hirschfeld</u></a>&nbsp;is the founder and CEO of&nbsp;<a href="https://rackn.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>RackN</u></a>, providing secure workflows and modular life-cycle automation for bare metal, edge, and cloud. Rob is a proponent of collaboration in the open source software industry. In this episode, he joins Ben Rometsch to share his insight and ideas from an infrastructure perspective on what needs solving and the potential outcomes. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>Appsmith W/ Founder And CEO Nikhil Nandagopal</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/jEkS-ssEX/media/JZaF7XzwH.mp3" length="47022511" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>jEkS-ssEX</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 11:18:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2939</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/appsmith-w-founder-and-ceo-nikhil-nandagopalc/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>As a company grows, internal tools start to play a bigger role, and these tools become harder to maintain. This is why <a href="https://www.appsmith.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Appsmith</a> was created. It's an open-source platform that lets you create these internal tools. Join Ben Rometsch as he talks to <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nikhil-nandagopal-05534241/?originalSubdomain=in" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Nikhil Nandagopal</a> about Appsmith. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>Meilisearch w/ Co-Founder Thomas Payet</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/9-AiuMKdj/media/X8t2HjuGU.mp3" length="46586603" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>9-AiuMKdj</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2022 10:54:05 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2912</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/meilisearch-with-co-founder-thomas-payet</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tpayet/?originalSubdomain=fr" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Thomas Payet</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, Co-founder &amp; COO of </span><a href="https://www.meilisearch.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);"><u>Meilisearch</u></a></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Sebastian Rindom, Co-Founder &amp; CEO @ Medusa</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/UrX1gFdgK/media/s3KP61nYq.mp3" length="41553096" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>UrX1gFdgK</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2597</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/sebastian-rindom-co-founder-ceo-medusa</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.medusajs.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(149, 79, 114);"><u>Medusa</u></a><span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">&nbsp;is an open source headless e-commerce platform founded by </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastianrindom/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(149, 79, 114);"><u>Sebastian Rindom</u></a><span style="color: rgb(0, 0, 0);">. The company provides software for sellers to develop a unique commerce experience. </span></p>]]></description></item><item><title>Peer Richelsen, Co-Founder &amp; Co-CEO @ Cal.com</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/aHuE7Keio/media/uBO0404lG.mp3" length="47733038" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>aHuE7Keio</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Mar 2022 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2983</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/peer-richelsen-co-founder-co-ceo-cal-com</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Cal.com offers scheduling for everyone. Ben Rometsch and the CEO of <a href="https://cal.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);"><u>Cal.com</u></a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/peer-richelsen-221233138/?originalSubdomain=de" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);"><u>Peer Richelsen</u></a>, give us a look at the nuts and bolts of this open source project. Peer goes back to the founding of the company, getting funded and how they approach integration with other apps. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>Video.js With Creator Steve Heffernan</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/bhZX2pKCtD/media/nlxXbc4SM.mp3" length="35550351" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>bhZX2pKCtD</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 14:16:52 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2222</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/video.js-with-creator-steve-heffernan</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>These days, video is everybody’s favorite mode of media consumption. But what really goes into video and the technology behind it? Today’s guest is video technology enthusiast, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/heffernan/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);"><u>Steve Heffernan</u></a>. Steve is the Co-Founder at <a href="https://mux.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);"><u>Mux</u></a>&nbsp;and Creator of <a href="https://videojs.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(5, 99, 193);"><u>Video.js</u></a>, a web video player built from the ground up for an HTML5 world. Steve gets deep into the complexities of the space and where it’s headed as it scales. The future is video. Learn all about the space and what Steve’s company is up to next by tuning in!</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Hoppscotch With Founder And CEO, Liyas Thomas</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/XNNK9OHVK/media/eacf_yCWo.mp3" length="41951344" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>XNNK9OHVK</guid><pubDate>Tue, 21 Dec 2021 10:53:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2621</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/hoppscotch-liyas-thomas/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://hoppscotch.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Hoppscotch</u></a>&nbsp;is an open-source API development ecosystem that gets you straight to the points and helps you create API requests faster. Join Ben Rometsch and his guest,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/liyasthomas/?originalSubdomain=in" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Liyas Thomas</u></a>, the Founder and CEO of Hoppscotch, as they dive into how Hoppscotch came to be. Discover how Liyas started it with a single post and how that post got viral. Learn how to find the right audience that knows what they want to do. Find out how Liyas created the clean and slick user interface of Hoppscotch and why it doesn't have a landing page. Finally, discover how he does business organically with his trusted team and outside developers across the world. Wait until you hear more about Hoppscotch. You’d want to start using it ASAP!</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Expo With Founder And CEO, Charlie Cheever</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/R7pexk47S/media/nMQ78d1_t.mp3" length="51011512" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>R7pexk47S</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 20:32:10 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3188</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/expo-charlie-cheever</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Co-Founder of Quora.com, early Facebook engineer and now CEO and Co-Founder of Expo, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/ccheever/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);"><u>Charlie Cheever</u></a> joins Ben Rometsch to talk about how Expo is helping engineers seamlessly release their products on all platforms instantly. </p>]]></description></item><item><title>Rill Data With Founder And CEO, Michael Driscoll</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/OT2aVgHwZ/media/XEoVzuNHu.mp3" length="37723754" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>OT2aVgHwZ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 11:35:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2358</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/rill-data-michael-driscoll</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Data is bigger than ever. In this episode,&nbsp;<a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/medriscoll/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Michael Driscoll</u></a>&nbsp;shares just where big data is heading and how the industry is changing with it. Michael is the Founder and CEO of&nbsp;<a href="https://www.rilldata.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Rill Data</u></a>&nbsp;and Co-founder of&nbsp;<a href="https://metamarkets.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Metamarkets</u></a>.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>Browserless: From Github Issue to Sustainable Business w/ Joel Griffith, Founder and CEO</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/Pvw-k2Z0o/media/B36SCo1Rw.mp3" length="46169438" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>Pvw-k2Z0o</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 12:49:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2886</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/browserless-joel-griffith</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">Ben sits down with the&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.browserless.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Browserless</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;founder and CEO&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/joel-griffith-93933332/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Joel Griffith</u></a>. Joel shares how he turned a github issue into a profitable business that helps thousands of companies around the world.</p>]]></description></item><item><title>HashiCorp&apos;s (@HashiCorp) journey from open source project to unicorn with Founder Mitchell Hashimoto (@mitchellh) and Ben Rometsch (@getflagsmith)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/FteaR8wjm/media/jTVK5Y-4d.mp3" length="44848625" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>FteaR8wjm</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 16:43:33 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2803</itunes:duration><link> https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/mitchell-hashimoto-founder-of-hashicorp-creator-of-vagrant-packer-serf-consul-terraform-vault-and-nomad</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/mitchellh" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Mitchell Hashimoto's</a> company<span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.hashicorp.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224); background-color: rgb(255, 255, 255);">HashiCorp</a> is the creator of <span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">Vagrant, Packer, Serf, Consul, Terraform, Vault, and Nomad. Together, these open source projects have over 100,000 stars on Github and exist to help engineers better </span>with consistent workflows to provision, secure, connect, and run any infrastructure for any application.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>12</itunes:episode></item><item><title>The founding story of Typesense (@typesense) with Co-Founder and CTO Jason Basco (@jasonbosco)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/Pd826sKdM/media/H33BUMRsy.mp3" length="49493029" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>Pd826sKdM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3093</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/jason-bosco-typesense</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify"><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">What does it take to build a good open-source search engine? Ben Rometsch, CEO of Flagsmith, sits down for a lively discussion on </span><a href="https://typesense.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Typesense</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">'s search engine technology with its co-creator, </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/jasonbosco/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(149, 79, 114);">Jason Bosco</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">. Jason discusses the origin of Typesense and their design choices, including the unusual choice of using C++ for its creation. We also hear about their decision to go open source and how the community is helping them refine their product. This is an episode you must not miss if you want to learn more about open source and search engine design.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>22</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Sebastien Lorber, Docusaurus</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/9Lzaso6Gz/media/dvecnnr5z.mp3" length="42761818" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>9Lzaso6Gz</guid><pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2673</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/sebastien-lorber-docusaurus</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://docusaurus.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Docusaurus</u></a>&nbsp;lead developer <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sebastienlorber/?locale=en_US" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Sebastien Lorber</u></a>&nbsp;has some interesting insights to share. As a freelance contractor, Sebastien leads the development of the Docusaurus open-source project for Facebook. Docusaurus is a static site generator that generates a modern single-page application from Markdown files so that website creators can focus on creating their content. </p>]]></description><itunes:episode>21</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Pablo Múzquiz, Penpot</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/10y7Q1Jp8/media/aIfe5Ikdn.mp3" length="44316243" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>10y7Q1Jp8</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Aug 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2770</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/pablo-muzquiz-penpot/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pruizmuzquiz/?originalSubdomain=es" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Pablo Múzquiz</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, CEO &amp; co-founder of </span><a href="https://penpot.app/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Penpot</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">. Penpot gives design freedom for teams. In this episode, Pablo takes Ben Rometsch behind the scenes on how they came up with Penpot. Join in the conversation and discover Penpot’s groundbreaking potential for designers. </span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>20</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Harsha, Co-Founder @ MinIO (min.io)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/CcXWtpPv4/media/SdYp2xC0K.mp3" length="33160483" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>CcXWtpPv4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2073</itunes:duration><link></link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">MinIO is  the #1 cloud-native open-source object store for enterprises. In this episode, Ben caught up with </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/harshavardhanar/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Harshavardhana</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, the co-founder of </span><a href="https://min.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">MinIO</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">. </span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>19</itunes:episode></item><item><title>The Founding Story of Jenkins (@jenkinsci) with the creator Kohsuke Kawaguchi and Ben Rometsch (getflagsmith)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/HhJpTPOjV/media/dO-AsC-cS.mp3" length="44469541" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>HhJpTPOjV</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2779</itunes:duration><link> https://flagsmith.com/podcast/kohsuke-kawaguchi-creator-of-jenkins-co-ceo-launchable</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify"><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">The open-source community was changed forever with the </span><a href="https://www.jenkins.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Jenkins</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);"> software project. Providing hundreds of plugins to be used for project building, deployment, and automation, it is the leading open-source automation server today. To explore this even further, Ben Rometsch goes back to the beginning by sitting down with its creator, </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/kohsukekawaguchi/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(149, 79, 114);">Kohsuke Kawaguchi</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">. He tells the story of how he was motivated to design such an open-source project, how it was conceptualized, and the silly origins of its name. The two also discuss their thoughts about software concepts that start with a commercial version only for someone to build its open-source counterpart. Kohsuke also shares his current life at Launchable, particularly about his mission to connect the Japanese tech scene to the western world.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>18</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Bjarne Christiansen, Co-Founder @ Realm</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/2Csv8PFe6/media/CGPx0gi48.mp3" length="38673790" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>2Csv8PFe6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2416</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/bjarne-christiansen-co-founder-realm</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify"><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">Open source is an ever-evolving field since technological innovation and demands will not stop as human life progresses, finding a useful open-source alternative to existing projects. This way, the work of a developer can be easier depending on the purpose they are after. Ben Rometsch talks with </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/bjchrist/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Bjarne Christiansen</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);"> to discuss the journey of how he built </span><a href="https://realm.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);">Realm</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, which offers a mobile database that is not only developer-friendly but also a useful alternative to SQLite and CoreData. He also shares how his partnerships with MongoDB and Firebase worked for him, as well as the company’s plans to transcend into the realm of the Internet of Things.</span></p><p><br></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>17</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Kasra Bigdeli, CapRover</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/-Dc7A8j4t/media/pI9Hn_cAR.mp3" length="38144653" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>-Dc7A8j4t</guid><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2384</itunes:duration><link>https://flagsmith.com/podcast/kasra-bigdeli-caprover/</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">One of the most important features of an open-source project is its high level of user-friendliness. Even if one has various complexities that allow for better application development or webserver management, something that's confusing and time-consuming will not be used as much by many. This is what&nbsp;</span><a href="https://caprover.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Kasra Bigdeli</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;had in mind when he started CapRover. He joins Ben Rometsch to share how this simple side hustle grew into an organized company, all to provide the most practical solutions to the biggest open-source projects and issues. Kasra also talks about how he addresses the never-ending requests and feedback from clients, how he chooses licenses for his projects, and which tools he uses to make his work much easier than usual.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>16</itunes:episode></item><item><title>OSS Capital&apos;s Vision for the Future of Open Source Software with JJ Jacks (@asynchio) and Ben Rometsch (getflagsmith)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/ZxHTSP7oT/media/djSIQpC0u.mp3" length="45507838" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>ZxHTSP7oT</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 13:56:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2844</itunes:duration><link> https://flagsmith.com/podcast/joseph-jj-jacks-oss-capital</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">In this episode, Ben Rometsch helps unravel this category by sitting down with&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/josephjacks/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Joseph Jacks</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;of&nbsp;</span><a href="https://oss.capital/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">OSS Capital</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;to learn more about what the funding ecosystem looks like for commercial open source companies. JJ is a huge COSS supporter and shares why he thinks this is the best time to be building a company in this space. </span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>15</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Mattermost&apos;s (@Mattermost) journey from open source to commercial success with Co-Founder and CEO Ian Tien (@iantien) and Ben Rometsch (@getflagsmith)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/jwPT55Vh9/media/tawtEg5rs.mp3" length="39624641" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>jwPT55Vh9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 11:24:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2477</itunes:duration><link> https://flagsmith.com/podcast/ian-tien-mattermost</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">In this episode, Ben Rometsch interviews&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/iantien/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Ian Tien</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, the CEO and co-founder of&nbsp;</span><a href="https://mattermost.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Mattermost</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, which has been referred to as the open-source alternative for Slack. Ian shares their genesis story in gaming, the challenges they encountered with scaling a messaging company, the applications they find useful, and more. </span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>14</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Nic Hourcard, Co-Founder of QuestDB</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/88wcMtfg9/media/Bz_CuU9XK.mp3" length="46139702" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>88wcMtfg9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2884</itunes:duration><link> https://flagsmith.com/podcast/nick-hourcard-questdb</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/nicolas-hourcard-b7349b37/?originalSubdomain=uk" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Nicolas Hourcard</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">&nbsp;saw this need for a high performance time-series database and decided to co-found&nbsp;</span><a href="https://questdb.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">QuestDB</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">. In this episode, he joins Ben Rometsch to share the genesis of this project and the problems they are trying to fix with the technology. </span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>13</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Torkel Ödegaard, Grafana Creator &amp; Project Lead</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/bJGYKvrpp/media/qsUIb4tWK.mp3" length="35565436" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>bJGYKvrpp</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2223</itunes:duration><link> https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/torkel-odegaard-grafana-creator-project-lead</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">Looking for observability dashboards that have the right balance between looking good, easy to use, powerful, and intuitive? Ben Rometsch has a web application just for you. In this episode, he sits down with the creator and project lead of&nbsp;</span><a href="https://grafana.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Grafana</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">,&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/torkel-odegaard?originalSubdomain=se" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);"><u>Torkel Ödegaard</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, to talk about how he started this company that offers a monitoring observability solution built on open-source components. He takes us inside into the work they put into creating a great user interface as well as the behind-the-scenes of meeting co-founders, finding the people to finance the deals, and scaling. Talking to others thinking of building a monitoring and observability company, Torkel then shares some advice on how to navigate the open-source industry and more.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>11</itunes:episode></item><item><title>David Heinemeier Hansson (DHH), Creator Of Ruby On Rails, Founder &amp; CTO At Basecamp &amp; HEY</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/SA6Cl3t9H/media/G68YLmNBP.mp3" length="61124341" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>SA6Cl3t9H</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 08:47:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3820</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/david-heinemeier-hansson-ruby-on-rails</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Released in 2004, <a href="https://rubyonrails.org/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Ruby on Rails</u></a>&nbsp;is an open-source web application framework written in Ruby. Created by <a href="https://dhh.dk/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>David Heinemeier Hansson</u></a>, the framework takes full advantage of the Ruby’s unique features to create a language that continues to be very approachable even after almost two decades of development. In this conversation with Ben Rometsch, David dives deep into the genesis and evolution of Ruby on Rails and talks about his other works in progress at <a href="https://basecamp.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Basecamp</u></a>&nbsp;and <a href="https://hey.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>HEY</u></a>. He also shares his prophetic and revolutionary insights on licensing, antitrust and other issues that matter to the open-source community.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>10</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Quinn Slack, CEO &amp; Co-Founder Of Sourcegraph</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/bS3H7aLbX/media/_N47M_sZb.mp3" length="40072157" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>bS3H7aLbX</guid><pubDate>Tue, 16 Mar 2021 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2494</itunes:duration><link>www.flagsmith.com/blog/quinn-slack-ceo-co-founder-of-sourcegraph</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Universal code search is an awesome tool that can make you a lot more efficient as a coder, but not many developers or companies use it. An open source alternative to Google Code Search, <a href="https://sourcegraph.com/search" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Sourcegraph</u></a>&nbsp;is on a mission to bring this underappreciated piece of software into every developer and every company that needs it. The company’s CEO, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/quinnslack/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Quinn Slack</u></a>&nbsp;joins Ben Rometsch on the show to share how Sourcegraph works with former Google developers to replicate some of the amazing features of Google’s internal code search tool that are not offered by most of the competition. He also talks about the initial struggle they had in offering a cloud service, their subsequent shift to self-hosting, and the difficult decision to go partially open source. A coder himself, Quinn believes that once developers start using code search, they wouldn’t be able to live without it again. But first, the challenge is to convince them to use it in the first place.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>9</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Robin Gustafsson, CEO @ k6</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/fnmCxJF5r/media/4R4v_hlTW.mp3" length="41237880" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>fnmCxJF5r</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Mar 2021 16:29:08 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2567</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/10-robin-gustafsson-ceo-k6</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Companies that have an open source component usually started out as open source and then developed an enterprise version of the software later. Load testing SaaS platform, <a href="https://k6.io/about" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>k6</u></a>&nbsp;approached its development the other way around – producing an interesting dynamic that has resulted to unique outcomes for the company. As CEO <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/robinegustafsson/?originalSubdomain=se" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Robin Gustafsson</u></a>&nbsp;relates in this conversation with Ben Rometsch, that entry into the relatively unknown territory of open source gave the k6 team a lot to argue about for some years, but it ultimately allowed them to create a business model that benefits from the best of both worlds. Interestingly, the company’s unique path has created a clear delineation between which of its components are open source and which are proprietary. Listen in and pick up some cool lessons from this company’s journey.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>8</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Maciej Zawadziński &amp; Piotr Korzeniowski of Piwik PRO</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/oYzla68H0/media/zoxqzqlpg.mp3" length="47949033" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>oYzla68H0</guid><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2021 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2986</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/07-matomo-piwik-pro</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>There is an ethical conundrum that revolves around the issue of data privacy when it comes to web analytics. Most marketers and businesses, especially the smaller ones, are naturally inclined to use Google Analytics because it offers high functionality for free. However, it does come with the price of data privacy and governments and other stakeholders are increasingly becoming aware of it. <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/zawadzinski?originalSubdomain=pl" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Maciej Zawadziński</u></a>&nbsp;was among the people at the forefront of the development of Piwik (now Matomo), an open source alternative to Google Analytics that focuses on privacy. In 2013, Maciej co-launched <a href="https://piwik.pro" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Piwik PRO</u></a>&nbsp;to offer support and consulting for users of the open source Piwik platform that weren't able to get the enterprise features they needed. In 2016, Piwik PRO went independent and shifted its focus on developing an enterprise version of its web analytics software. Together with his COO <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/pkorzeniowski/?originalSubdomain=pl" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Piotr Korzeniowski</u></a>, Maciej joins Ben Rometsch to talk about the company’s genesis, core philosophy and future direction.</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>7</itunes:episode></item><item><title>David Cramer, Co-Founder and CTO, Sentry (Sentry.io)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/k_pjGaJsV/media/icyDMU7Sv.mp3" length="50552087" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>k_pjGaJsV</guid><pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3149</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/06-sentry</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Co-Founder and CTO of Sentry, David Cramer joins Ben Rometsch on this episode to talk about his journey from a side project of 70 lines of open source code to the most widely adopted open source crash reporting platform in the world. </p>]]></description><itunes:episode>6</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Heather Meeker, Founding Partner @ OSS Capital</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/dAfLeFRA2/media/f_aGe7CN7.mp3" length="46783517" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>dAfLeFRA2</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jan 2021 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2920</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/blog/heather-meeker-founder-partner--oss-capital</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Legal systems for almost any industry tends to follow innovation. In open source, that lag has been even more pronounced due to the pace of change and increased complexity. OSS Capital founder, <a href="https://heathermeeker.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(0, 0, 255);"><u>Heather Meeker</u></a>, has followed the evolution of open source licensing over the course of her 25 year legal career. Sitting down with host Ben Rometsch in this episode, she describes how the legal community is coping with the ever increasing complexities and shares her opinion on the role of legal going forward. This is an extremely informative and insightful conversation for anyone that is thinking about software licensing and how to strike the right balance with the community. Check it out!</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>5</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Tom Moor, Founder @ Outline (GetOutline.com)</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/oliUQ1BMN/media/rxo1TpEgm.mp3" length="38344763" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>oliUQ1BMN</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 11:00:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2360</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/04-outline</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">Transitioning from a closed source project to open source has its own challenges.  Shedding light into the process, Ben Rometsch invites </span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/tom-moor-b6213b1ba/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);"><u>Tom Moor</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, the founder of </span><a href="https://www.getoutline.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(17, 85, 204);"><u>Outline</u></a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">. Outline is becoming a widely adopted knowledge-base for leading companies around the world. It has grown incredibly fast with over 10,000 stars on Github and poised to continue it's growth with recent major products in this space being sunset. Together, they talk about Tom’s journey into starting his company as a side project, choosing the right software license and the associated risk of cutting off marketing share, and figuring out a way to build a business from the community.</span></p>]]></description><itunes:episode>4</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Michael DeHaan: Founder, Ansible</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/aDVRBo2HV/media/WKL8CwcV8.mp3" length="54825091" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>aDVRBo2HV</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2020 22:07:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>3398</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/03-ansible</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.ansible.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Ansible&nbsp;</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">was created to make automating IT infrastructure simple. In this episode, we are joined by&nbsp;</span><a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/michaeldehaan/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank" style="color: rgb(74, 110, 224);">Michael DeHaan</a><span style="color: rgb(14, 16, 26);">, founder of Ansible, to take us through a wide-ranging conversation. He talks about his beginnings in the open-source community at Redhat, why he started Ansible as a side project and his thoughts on the open-source community's state.&nbsp;</span></p><p class="ql-align-justify"><br></p><p class="ql-align-justify">Technologies Discussed: Ansible, Redhat, VMWare, IBM, Virtualization, DNS Management, Up To Date, Chef, Puppet, Configuration Tools, Open Source, SSH, Cisco, YAML, Automation, CI/CD, GitHub, Agile, Kubernetes, Cobbler, Linux, React Native, Source Code</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>3</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Uku Taht And Marko Saric: Co-Founders, Plausible</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/KAtkSSget/media/hPHwp3Fsh.mp3" length="42636309" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>KAtkSSget</guid><pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2020 21:23:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2635</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/02-plausible</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p>Uku and Marko are the Co-Founders of Plausible...and they've never actually met in person. Plausible is an open source alternative to Google Analytics and a project that was launched in 2018. Uku was inspired to launch a project on IndieHackers and share his progress with the world. Eventually he decided to open the product up to the open source community. About 6 months ago, Uku and Marko decided to team up as co-founders, but due to the pandemic they haven't met face-to-face. Since launching the open source project in 2019, they've grown in popularity as more and more teams are looking at alternatives for analytics.</p><p><br></p><p>Technologies Discussed: Google Analytics, GitHub, Ansible, Flagsmith, Elixir</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>2</itunes:episode></item><item><title>Paul Dix: Co-Founder &amp; CTO, InfluxDB</title><enclosure url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/DAM3DIbNk/media/EN80MVc7J.mp3" length="46153258" type="audio/mpeg"></enclosure><guid>DAM3DIbNk</guid><pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:43:00 GMT</pubDate><itunes:duration>2848</itunes:duration><link>https://www.flagsmith.com/podcast/01-influxdb</link><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit><description><![CDATA[<p class="ql-align-justify">In this episode, Paul Dix talks about the origins of InfluxDB, how they’ve built it into a massive project and where they are heading next. Paul shares great insights on how they found early product-market fit, decided to build a database as a product and why they saw a unique opportunity for their technology with the open source community.&nbsp;</p><p class="ql-align-justify"><br></p><p class="ql-align-justify">Technologies discussed: Redis, MongoDB, Rust, Influx Database, Flagsmith, DataDog, Apache, Database, JavaScript, API, Open Source, SQL, MySQL</p>]]></description><itunes:episode>1</itunes:episode></item></channel></rss>